plagiarismtoday.com 2019-05-25

# Privacy Policy - Plagiarism Today

## Who we are

This site is operated by Jonathan Bailey and our website address is  https://www.plagiarismtoday.com.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact forms

This site uses multiple contact forms that email the information entered information into to the site’s owners. That information may also be temporarily stored on the site’s servers in the form of log files. That data is retained indefinitely both in log file form and in email by our email provider.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

In addition to server logs, we also use Google Analytics (https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en) and Jetpack Analytics (https://jetpack.com/support/privacy/) to track traffic and other statistics. You may read their privacy policies at the links provided.

## Who we share your data with

In addition to analytics and embedded content, we use Distil Networks (https://www.distilnetworks.com/privacy/) to provide content delivery services and to provide security tools for the site.

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

Likewise, if you register for the email newsletter, your email address (and no other personal data) will be retained indefinitely until you unsubscribe from the newsletter, when it is immediately deleted.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service. It is also verified accessed by Distil Networks (https://www.distilnetworks.com/privacy/), which provides content delivery services and security services for this site.

## Your contact information

Jonathan Bailey  
3920 General DeGaulle Dr.  
New Orleans, LA 70131  
Email: jonathan@plagiarismtoday.com  
Phone: 1.504.272.7524

## Additional information

### How we protect your data

In addition to following industry-standard security protocols, Plagiarism Today is protected by Distil Networks, a content delivery network that restricts automated access to the site and all of the content on it, including any stored personal information.

### What data breach procedures we have in place

If a data breach is detected, we will notify users both via the site and email newsletter within 72 hours.

### What third parties we receive data from

We receive no data from third parties other than analytics information discuss above.

### What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data

We have no automated decision making or profiling.

### Industry regulatory disclosure requirements

We have no industry regulatory disclosures.
